Create your first world. Describe the world, compare candidates, and build a Sketch.
Choose Generate a new world, then Writing and world building.
Describe the world in a few sentences.
Review the recognised ideas. Apply all to use them in the brief.
Find strong matches to compare possible starting worlds.
Search time omitted. Compare the candidates and choose a favourite.
Continue to review your chosen seed.
Continue to Build when the seed suits your world.
Choose Sketch world for a quick first pass.
Start the build. The app simulates the world in the background.
Build time omitted. Choose Open in studio to explore your world.